wallstreetwindow.com 2018-10-27

# None

Wallstreetwindow.com takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this [ privacy policy primer](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Privacy_policy) by Wikipedia to learn more about privacy policies in general.

## Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.  This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for internal use.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, Wallstreetwindow.com uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

## Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of [ web browser privacy management](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/114836) links for Chrome may also be useful.

## Google Adsense and Doubleclick DART Cookie

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. The DoubleClick DART cookie is one cookie used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a our website and either view or click an ad, a cookie may be dropped on the end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web. 

Google's use of cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**  
** For more information on Google see its and  [ content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google: Advertising & Privacy").   

## Facebook Advertising and Audience Profiles

WallStreetwindow also uses Facebook cookies to enable Facebook to track traffic and build what it calls audience profiles. 

At times ads are run to people cookied in these audience profiles through Facebook. For information on Facebook's tracking systems go to its [Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

**Links to Third Part Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites.  You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

## Contact Information

If you have concerns or questions about this privacy policy go to our [contact page](http://www.wallstreetwindow.com/contact) for further clarification.
